首先将TextView标签改为ListView标签
You should have changed the TextView into a ListView element.
然后将text属性删掉  因为我们不再需要它了
Then you can remove this text attribute because you don't need it anymore.
之前我们讲过Sunshine的布局框架  你一定还记得天气列表要占据整个屏幕吧
Now from the UX Mocks, you'll remember that the list takes up the whole screen,
所以我们要将layout_width和layout_height的属性设置成match_parent
so we want to set the width and height to be match_parent.
这样可以使ListView填满
That will make the ListView match the dimensions of its parent,
RelativeLayout父布局
which is this RelativeLayout.
那又要去哪找到这个RelativeLayout的父布局呢
And to find out the parent of this RelativeLayout,
它实际上是在activity_main.xml里
it's actually in this activity_main XML file
因为该Activity会包含fragment_main.xml里的内容
because the fragment is contained within the activity.
在activity_main.xml中  我们看到layout_height和layout_width的值也是match_parent
Within this file, we see that this view is also match_parent for height and width.
现在我们就可以肯定  天气ListView一定会占据整个屏幕
So now we can confirm that the ListView actually will take up the full screen.
回到fragment_main.xml  我们向ListView加一个id属性
Going back to the fragment_main file, we can add the id,
值为listview_forecast
listview_forecast, onto the ListView.
既然父布局只包含了一个子控件
And then, since this layout only contains one child,
我们可将RelativeLyout改为FrameLayout来简化布局
we can simplify the layout by changing this into a FrameLayout.